I am Mai Kanazawa of Morisaka46.
Now, where am I?
The correct answer is
Ta-da!
I'm at ESCON Field Hokkaido!
Oh, my camera's a little shaky.
The reason why I'm here today is,
The day before yesterday, I appeared on several TV programs in Hokkaido,
And I still have more to do today,
The important thing is that the most important fox dance is today,
I have come to Escondido Field.
I will be appearing on live TV in the morning,
I'm going to start getting ready right away.
I'm off!
I want to make sure everyone is satisfied with my performance.
Yes, I just need that kind of information already. I don't care what's gone, that's all I have to say.
I will be sending you the spring technicals for the dream goal park, the local round-about.
It's been raining all morning from rehearsal to everything.
That's right.
Mr. Hanakawa, you are a fine lady.
Wow, thank you. I'll have you be sunny.
It's true.
Thank you for starting so early.
I look forward to working with you all day.
Good luck today.
Thank you, Hanakawa-chan.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad.
Well then, we're inside the new stadium. Let's go around.
Chikara-san.
Like a painting of a player's shoulder.
It's cool, isn't it? It's more than cool when it's painted.
There are no customers yet, but there are a lot of customers, too.
Oh, my God!
Can I look at this?
Can I look at it?
Don't look at it yet.
It's amazing.
That's amazing.
Jump!
Oh, my gosh!
I can't show it too big, but...
Athletes are practicing here.
It's so big!
It's very close. I'm closer to the players than I thought.
They are almost there.
Oh, Mr. Freep is here.
He is here. He is here. Mr. Freep.
He's so cute.
It's amazing.
It's so big, but you can see it.
Wow, it's kind of fun already.
Maybe I'm a little nervous. It's pretty swishy. Oh, it smells good. I wonder what it is.
Croquettes? Do you have croquettes?
We do croquettes.
I'm really happy. I'm so happy.
What should I do? It's so close.
I can't believe I can see it here.
I'm so happy.
I haven't been to Kyushu since the last time I danced the fox dance at Sapporo Dome,
It's very different from Sapporo Dome.
It's a lot bigger,
I feel like the brand is more compact than Sapporo Dome.
Look, it's close.
There is also this.
This one says "pin badge". That one seems to be a pin badge.
Wow, there are a lot of them.
Look, there's a guy who helped me in the Prospey game.
Shironobu-kun, who helped me in the Prospey game, is here.
It's been a long time.
I see.
This way,
From 1974 to 1987.
Wow!
They're all listed in chronological order.
That's amazing. That's amazing!
Oh, here's Ralfisch!
Wow! It's amazing, there are so many fighters and ex-fighters in WNC!
And here is Corona, where Manager Kuriyama used to work until recently.
Oh, Otani!
Oh, there's Manager Murakami!
This way.
And this is Escondido Field Hokkaido.
This is the Escon Field Hokkaido. This is fun!
I haven't seen all of them yet, but the one below...
But if you see this one too, you can trace the history, I'm sure.
Wow, it's huge! Look at this!
It's amazing!
All I can say is "wow" here, but wow!
This might be the most open area here.
A lot of players have started practicing here.
Lots of people here!
This seems to be the goods store.
It's so big!
It's a big bag.
I want one!
I want a hoodie... I want a hoodie...
I want it so bad!
Oh, my God!
There's so much stuff, I'll definitely buy it.
I'm ready to buy today.
I'm serious.
I'm really ready to buy it!
This is the view of Gaia colors!
Look at that!
It's huge!
It says "Fighters" here, "Fine" there, "Fine" all over the place.
It says "Fighters." Cool!
I used to see this on TV.
Look at this!
Daravish and Otani. How cool!
Oh, man...
I wonder if I can get a closer look.
It's amazing!
It looks like he painted it by hand.
They're so big!
Look at it. Oh, wow.
It's amazing, isn't it?
I don't need one either.
So I've been looking around now, and I'm going to practice fox dancing with Mr. Karl the Fighter.
I have a fox dance practice with Mr. Karl, the fighter, so I'm going to head over there now.
I'll do my best.
Well, now that she's here, let's all practice the fox dance together.
Mr. Kanazawa's escort will be our first guest to fox dance with us today.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. We're the first guests to dance the fox dance with us.
That's great.
Please make it exciting.
Well, I'm going to try it once in a row.
Fighters, Karl, please line up for the fox dance.
I'll go first.
Okay, I'll go.
Please do.
Thank you very much.
Okay.
Congratulations.
I think it's safe.
Good luck with the show.
Yes, please.
We'll be waiting here for the show.
We'll be waiting here, and the door will actually be closed.
And then it's out.
The door will bop open and come from here to this tree.
Just now, right there is the form base.
And there's the left and right side.
There's also a fighter grub up there.
Standing on the bare side is roughly where the net is over there now.
This is where the big net is.Around this big net.
That's where you'll be standing naked.
The net in the back? The front net?
The front net.
The front side net, okay.
The bare side of the net.
Yes, sir.
Yes, I just finished practicing the fox dance.
I was a little nervous.
I guess you call it a practice room.
It was the same kind of room we usually use for lessons,
I felt very familiar with the room,
It was the same kind of room I usually use for lessons,
But everyone was really kind, just like last time,
I was given courage. I was really encouraged.
I hope to make no mistakes and captivate everyone with my smile.
And I have another live broadcast coming up,
I will study a lot and talk a lot in the live broadcast.
So, I will start preparing for the live broadcast.
Also!
Naito-san trick startoriginal
Thank you so much for your support!
Best regards
Pleased to meet you.
I am Shigeru Sato. Pleased to meet you.
Yes, please.
Please give me your support.
There are people cheering for you.
Here you are.
I was so close, I couldn't even get my stomach right.
BANG BANG BANG!
Wow, a great one!
I wonder if it's like this, Rose.
The one that ends how it will end when the fighters are active.
I might definitely be vocal now.
Not at all anymore.
We were discussing it.
I'm so glad you could speak up at all.
Yes, I just changed into my costume for the fox dance.
Look at this.
It has a tail.
So cute!
I was on the sideline of the live broadcast during the game.
so I couldn't take pictures.
I did a lot of talking and here I am now.
I'm almost done with the fox dance.
So I'm a little nervous now.
Don't make any mistakes.
With a smile on my face
I'm going to make everyone fall in love with me.
Yes, I will.
Okay, Kana-san.
Yes, sir.
This side.
Yes.
Please.
The last time was amazing, wasn't it?
That pressure has been there for a long time, hasn't it?
So I am very anxious.
I also want to show something that is a little more refined.
For now, I will do my best to dance with a smile on my face.
Thank you very much.
If you have any requests, please let me know.
Please take care of them.
please.
Ending
Thank you very much
Thank you very much.
what the hell?
I'm glad
Thank you very much.
I'm nervous
Here we go.
Cheers.
Thank you very much.
We're done.
Oh, my God.
Just now...
My heart is still in knots.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to go back to the live broadcast now. I'll do my best.
Justice is Justice. It's English for Justice.
Did he say "Justice"? No, I didn't.
Okay, so work is done.
I was only able to watch the game until halfway through, and then the live broadcast ended.
I'm going to watch the game until the end.
I hope they win. I've been hoping.
The day started early in the morning.
I'm really happy that I was able to do the fox dance, which was the most important part of the day for me.
I don't know... it's something I'll remember for the rest of my life, and also...
I learned a lot from doing a live broadcast for the first time, and it made me want to learn more about baseball.
I want to know more about baseball.
There's another game tomorrow, so I'm going back to Tokyo to watch it.
I'll be back home a little late.
But I will do my best so that I can come back to Hokkaido again.
Thank you very much for joining me today.
Please subscribe to my channel and give me a rating!
Bye, bye, bye!